// This is the file that contains all the question, answer and point value data.

var json = [{
"question": "What mode of transportation would you be? ", 
"answers": ["Plane", "Train", "Bicycle", "Boat", "Car", "Pedestrian", "Hoverboard", "Monorail"],
"points": [32,24,12,9,8,7,2,1]
},
{
"question": "I knew I had made it when...", 
"answers": ["Designated parking spot","Had chief of staff","assistant always knew location","Won WTS Philly WOman of the year","bathroom in my office","stopped hearing my name at work"],
"points": ["JC","SP","SM","LR","DGS","VS"]
},
{
    "question": "What is the thing that most people do not \"get\" about your job?", 
    "answers": ["PEOPLES' LIVES IN YOUR HANDS","most roads/bridges not state's","always have to be \"on\" in public","not just roads and bridges","that it is a job!","have less power than they think"],
    "points": ["JC","SP","SM","LR","DGS","VS"]
    },
{
"question": "If I was not doing this job, I would be doing... ", 
"answers": ["Professor","teaching engineers, policymakers","sleeping in later","Audition for \"Amazing Race\"","teaching","no idea"],
"points": ["JC","SP","SM","LR","DGS","VS"]
},
{
"question": "Have you mastered the art of saying \"NO\"?", 
"answers": ["No", "Yes", "working on it!", "is this a trick question?"],
"points": [44,30,25,1]
},
{
"question": "What are some of the ways female advocates can make a difference?", 
"answers": ["BRING OUT ASPIRING TALENT","refuse to be only female at table","help other women be visible","Speak up, help others","share your story and mentor","support other women"],
"points": ["JC","SP","SM","LR","DGS","VS"]
},
{
"question": "What are some of the ways male advocates can make a difference?", 
"answers": ["MENTORING","model respectful interactions","acknowledge women's comments","open mind, focus on opportunities","attend WTS","speak up and join conversation"],
"points": ["JC","SP","SM","LR","DGS","VS"]
},
{
"question": "What is your favorite part of your job?", 
"answers": ["WORKING WITH STAFF","designing funding programs","shifting money around to spend it","Advancing diversity","the people","the mission"],
"points": ["JC","SP","SM","LR","DGS","VS"]
},
{
"question": "One thing my friends and family always tell me to do/not do", 
"answers": ["Relax", "Say no", "Drink less coffee", "Be safe", "stop talking", "be assertive", "stop checking emails", "don't sing"],
"points": [33,17,13,9,8,4,3,2]
},
{
    "question": "Name one character trait that helped prepare you for leadership", 
    "answers": ["COURAGE!","empathy","understanding all sides","a sense of humor","compassion","be humble"],
    "points": ["JC","SP","SM","LR","DGS","VS"]
    },
    {
    "question": "What was your dream job as a kid?", 
    "answers": ["NUCLEAR PHYSICIST","engineer","mapmaker","truck driver","singer","truck driver"],
    "points": ["JC","SP","SM","LR","DGS","VS"]
    },
{
"question": "Who inspires you?", 
"answers": ["Family members", "women leaders", "religious leader", "sheryl sandberg", "michelle obama", "rina cutler", "leslie richards", "gloria steinem"],
"points": [28,20,16,12,8,1,1,1]
},
{
    "question": "What was the best/worst decision you ever made?", 
    "answers": ["leading the DMV","secretary for moderate rep. gov","getting new office furniture","running for elected office","having children/majoring in acct.","pursuing current position"],
    "points": ["JC","SP","SM","LR","DGS","VS"]
    },
    {
    "question": "What was your dream job as a kid?", 
    "answers": ["to \"up the bar\"","(sadly) still not being token woman","understanding all generations","staying true to yourself","work/life balance","work/life balance"],
    "points": ["JC","SP","SM","LR","DGS","VS"]
    },
{
"question": "If you came to my house, you would have __________ for dinner", 
"answers": ["pasta", "something grilled", "pizza/take out", "fish", "stir fry", "tacos", "thai", "popcorn and wine"],
"points": [35,18,17,9,8,4,2,1]
}];
